

ABOUT ME

I'm a passionate video game programmer with a solid background in **object-oriented programming**.

I have worked at **Melbot**, where I was involved in game development and **publishing for consoles**, as well as handling their **ports**.

Additionally, I have gained experience working for **Magnetic**, where I focused on **mobile game** development and contributed to a **live project**.

Furthermore, I successfully **launched** my own **Android game** and completed several internships. I'm a very enterprising person, outgoing and eager for new experiences.

CONTACT

t 636 98 24 40

Barcelona

marina.chava24@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English: Advanced

Spanish: Native

Catalan: Native

LINKS

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marina-chavarria-gonzalez/

Marina Chavarria González

GAME PROGRAMMER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Game Programmer - Magnetic

April 2023 - October 2023

- Development of the live game "Art Heist Puzzle".
- Implementation of code for the client-server communication.
- Developed significant features for a live game.
- Actively applied dependency injection in the codebase.
- Debugged complex problems in existing code base.
- Participated in design meetings with other team members to discuss ideas for future content.
- Integrated third-party libraries into existing projects to extend functionality.

Console Game Programmer - Melbot

January 2022 - April 2023

Unannounced - Pc/Console multiplayer game

- Developed gameplay functionality for an online game.
- Make an audio management system for all SFX and base music for the project.
- Implement the FMOD system in the project and make custom code for it.
- Program customized packages for the base project.
- Implementation and programming of the UI system.

My Little Pony: A Maretime Bay Adventure

- Responsible for the port of MY LITTLE PONY: A Maretime Bay Adventure for the Play Station 5, following the publisher's guidelines.
- Working on the final development of My Little Pony: A Maretime Bay Adventure.
- Debugging the game to enhance its performance and resolve existing bugs.
- Working with the Nintendo SDK and Xbox to assist in the development of the other platform ports.

Other projects

- Developed a tool for creating levels that was highly flexible, allowing designers and artists to seamlessly incorporate their artwork into the tool, with the map adapting to the art.
- VFX and SFX tools to help artists implement the art in an unannounced game.

FORMATION

Videogame Programming and Design | Tecnocampus Pompeu Fabra 2018-2023

SKILLS

- C# C+
- Unity Unreal Engine
 - Lua Python

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Attention to detail
- Problem-Solving
- Time Managment
- Teamwork
- Adaptability